# 今天我朋友就是我们涂总
Today my friend Mr Tu
# 从珠海一千多公里回来看我们
Traveled all the way from Zhuhai for about 1000 kilometers to see us.
# 到我们工作室这边来看一下
He has come to our studio to take a look.
# 今天我来带他们参观一下
I'll give them a tour today.
# 这里面就是餐厅
This is the restaurant.
# 冬天比较好夏天这里面很热
Winter is better. Summer is too hot in here.
# 以前这里面是做餐馆的 桌子椅子都在
This used to be a restaurant. The tables and chairs are still here.
# 这里做农家乐是最好的
This is the best place to do "Nongjiale" (agritourism).
# 这边水冷的风扇坏了 开起的话还好
The water-cooling fan here is broken. It's fine when it's on.
# 这里以前是餐厅
This used to be a restaurant.
# 看一下我们的工作室
Take a look at our studio.
# 这里面很乱 才拍了开水白菜
It's a mess in here. I just finished the shooting of "Kaishui Baicai".
# 拍就在这里拍噶
Most of shooting is in here.
# 我们拍就在这里拍的
We shot it right here.
# 这儿是架电影机在这里拍
Here's the movie camera position.
# 架在这里拍
Put it up here.
# 现在是很乱 上一次拍了菜还没有打整
It's a mess. It wasn't properly cleaned after last shooting.
# 拍了开水白菜的
the "Kaishui Baicai".
# 以后我想这里没有拍视频了
If I am not shooting videos in the future.
# 开餐厅就把这些灶拉到餐厅里去
All the equipment can be used in any restaurant kitchen.
# 完全可以啊
Absolutely.
# 啊
Hmm.
# 以后不开餐厅做加工房也可以啊
It's okay if you don't want to open a restaurant, this can be a good food workshop.
# 嗯
Hmm.
# 就是加工后勤的一些东西啊这些所有东西
All the food manufacturing and logistics stuff.
# 如果是普通的锅你猜这锅烧开要烧好久
If it's an ordinary pot, guess how long it takes to boil it.
# 这一盆
This one.
# 平时五分钟 五分钟要得到不
Usually five minutes. Five minutes?
# 我这个30秒就把它搞定了
I got this one down in 30 seconds.
# 真的诶
Really?
# 估计的话就是30秒钟就开了
It should be boiling in about 30 seconds.
# 这个也很适合你炒料
It's also good if you fry the soup base.
# 你说炒料有个什么弊端安
What's the downside for frying soup base?
# 上面有个机器
There's a machine up there.
# 有个机器啊
A machine.
# 有个机器转起来
There's a machine that spins.
# 走嘛 我们去逛哈老板的果园嘛
Let's go and see the orchard of the place owner.
# 看哈他的果园
Look at his orchard.
# 这个葡萄园好大的哈
This grape farm is huge, huh?
# 哇塞 你看上面好多那些
Wow, look at all those up there.
# 是不是很甜
Isn't that sweet?
# 好吃哈
Yummy.
# 我们经常去农家乐摘葡萄 摘草莓
We used to go to the farmhouse to pick grapes and strawberries.
# 这儿出来就是我们的后门
It's our back door out of here.
# 这是啥子安
What's this?
# 这是火锅底料
It's the hotpot soup base.
# 这个我们卖得最好 前段时间应该卖了
This is our best seller. These days, we should have sold...
# 卖了一二十万份了
Already sold more than 100 thousand of them.
# 到现在
up until now.
# 花椒
Sichuan peppercorns
# 这个花椒好麻哦
This peppercorn is so numb.
# 这个花椒厉害
This is awesome.
# 这个花椒没得杂质的你看这下面
This peppercorn is unadulterated. Look down here.
# 这没得那种
This peppercorn...
# 没得那种黑壳壳得噶
Dose not have any of those black shell.
# 没得籽的 没得渣渣 没得花椒刺的 啥子都没得
No seeds, no scraps, no pepper thorns, only the peppercorns.
# 有专门给你提供的厂商
You have a special vendor?
# 这是我们本地的花椒
This is our local peppercorn.
# 这海椒才巴适 二娃
These chillies are the best, brother.
# 这弄得好精细哦 头头尾尾都全部剪过的
It's so delicate, it's all cut out at the end.
# 嗯
Hmm.
# 尾巴上也剪了的
It's cut off at the tail.
# 尾巴也剪了的
The stem's cut too.
# 头头尾尾剪了的嘛
They are so neat and tidy.
# 这个纯手工来剪的噶
This one was cut by hand?
# 嗯 机器机器
No, machine, machine.
# 牛肉啊 冷吃牛肉
Beef, cold serving beef.
# 我以为兔
I thought it's rabbit.
# 自贡做冷吃兔 冷吃牛肉
In Zigong we make Cold serving rabbit and cold serving beef.
# 冷吃兔做得出名点
Cold serving rabbit is so famous.
# 每天现去拉牛肉回来做的
We buy fresh beef every day in order to make this.
# 这个是什么辣度的安
What's the hot level on this one?
# 中辣
Medium level of spiciness
Medium level
# 嗯
Hmm.
# 这种辣度差不多了
It's the perfect hot level.
# 有牛肉的香味
The beef aroma is still in there.
# 嗯 你再辣点的话你吃不了了
Well, if it's too spicy, you won't be able to feel the aroma.
# 我们这个不像其它打开海椒多
Our beef don't have that much chili as the others.
# 海椒一半肉一半 我们基本是纯肉
They have a half chili and half meat. We're mostly pure meat.
# 嗯 这儿只是预包装的一个包装（地）
Well, here is the pre-packing and logistic place.
# 还有两个加工厂的 生产车间
There are also two manufacturing facilities.
# 差不多有一年了
It's been almost a year.
# 嗯
Hmm.
# 真的差不多一年了
It's been almost a year.
# 紫苏噶
Is it zisu？
# 这个不是紫苏 叫藿香
This isn't zisu. It's huoxiang. (herbs)